

SLAVA BARANOK

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



CONTACTS

- Minsk, Belarus
- mr.baranok.slava@gmail.com
- +375 (33) 901-84-35

ABOUT ME

I'm frontend developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript. Knowledge in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. I improving my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with new technologies, such as React Native. I usually spend my free time learning new technology, Codewars and improving my English with a tutor. Open to your suggestions.

SKILLS

- React
- Storybook
- Redux
- Unit-test
- Typescript
- SASS
- Javascript
- GIT
- React Native HTML / CSS
- Material-UI
 REST API
- Axios

ENGLISH

• A2 (Pre-intermediate) in progress

WORK EXPERIENCE

MY PROJECT AS FRONTEND **DEVELOPER (PART-TIME)**

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

CARDS

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, Axios, React-Router-dom, Yup

TODO LIST

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, MUI, Axios, React-Router-dom

SOCIAL NETWORK

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Axios, React Hook Form, React-Router-dom

«SKARB-BIO» (FULL-TIME) Sales-manager

2018 - 2022

- Sale of web service for production automation.
- Meeting with the head of the organization and offering our services.
- Service learning and Employee training.

EDUCATION

2021-2022 | IT-INCUBATOR

Frontend developer (React/Redux/Typescript/JS)

2021 | Freecodecamps (JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures)

2010-2015 | Belarusian State Agricultural Academy